Previously on desperate housewives...
前情提要
Your spleen has wandered close to your heart.
你的脾在向心脏偏移
We're gonna take it out.
需要切除
Get your insurance figured out by then
提前把保险办好
[There was the bad news]
有些是坏消息
It's the cop I want you to talk to
我是要你去跟警察谈
His name is Solomon
他叫Solomon
???  daughter
这是她女儿的档案
[The discomforting news]
令人不安的消息
Thanks
谢谢
Are you hiding someone in your house?
你家里是不是藏了谁？
Tell me your secret,I'll understand
把秘密告诉我,我会理解
OK
好吧
[and the news no one should know]
还有一些消息,谁也不该知道
But you tell me yours first
不过得先把你的秘密告诉我
Once a month,the (???) seciety
每个月
would attend a semi-formal lunch at the home of Maxine Bennett.
大家都会到Maxine Bennett家里 参加一次半正式的午宴
Everyone loves these elegant get-togethers
这样典雅的聚会很受大家欢迎
Everyone that is,
虽然大家都喜欢
but a certain red headed housewive who is convinced Maxine was a liar
一位红发主妇却认定Maxine说了谎
You see,Maxine like to brag that she did all her own cooking
Maxine喜欢吹嘘所有的菜肴 都由她亲手烹饪
and because each course was served promptly,
也正因为每道菜的迅速更换
presented with flare
色香味全
and it was positively mouth watering
让人垂涎欲滴
Bree knew Maxine had had some help
Bree便肯定了Maxine请了帮手
and sadly for Maxine...
Maxine的不幸在于...
Bree intended to prove it
Bree打算证明自己的想法
Maxine,once again,this entire lunch is just out the swirl
Maxine,这顿饭实在太让人难忘了
I just have to get the number of your caterer
我一定得把你厨师的电话要来
What a nice compliment.
多好的赞扬
No,I'm afraid this is all my doing
不过,这都是我一人之劳
This was a triumph,an absolute triumph
这是次盛典,绝对的盛典
Oh,come on,do you honestly expect us to believe
拜托,你真以为我们会相信
that you had the time to prepare a six-course meal for ten women
你会有时间给10个人准备6道菜？
Even I couldn't make this and have time to get ready for a party
连我都做不到 更别提还要准备派对
Well,perhaps you're just not as organized as I am
也许,你的组织性没有我的强
If you excuse me
我离开一下
Bree,what's got into you?
Bree  你是怎么了
I have the same recipe for English plum pudding
我有一套完全一样的 葡萄干布丁菜谱
It takes six hours to prepare
准备起来要花6个小时
How would you have time to make all this and everything else that we ate today
怎么可能有时间准备 这些外加我们今天吃到的其他东西？
This's not the pudding of an honest woman
这布丁绝对不是 出自一个诚实女人的手
FBI,open up
FBI 开门
What on earth...
究竟怎么了...
looking for a Maxine Bennett
我们要找一位Maxine Bennett
I'm Maxine
我就是Maxine
We have a warrant. This is the premier's mail
我们有许可证 这里是总理的邮件
A warrant? I'm in the middle of a luncheon
许可证？我正在用午餐呢啊
Over here
在这儿
Found her
找到了
Maxine Bennett,you are under arrest,
Maxine Bennett  你被捕了
for involuntary servitude
强制劳役罪
Is this the woman who locked you up?
就是她把你锁起来的吗
Bree,what's going on?
Bree  到底怎么回事
Well,I'm not sure,but I think Maxine had a slave
我不清楚 不过我想Maxine窝藏了奴隶
I can't believe it,I just can't believe it
不敢相信  简直不敢相信
[But Bree could,
不过Bree知道
you see,for her
对她来说
,the proof was in the pudding]
一切证据都藏在了布丁里
-------------------------- www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents --------------------------
-=伊甸园YTET字幕组=- 翻译: Bryan,小公窬,Jean,午夜飞行 校对: 午夜飞行 时间轴：Starry
Desperate housewives Season 2 Episode 14
欲乱绝情妻 第二季 第十四集
[The world is filled with unlikely friendships]
世上充满了反常的友情
make absolutely no sense at all]
如不仔细观察,这些搭配毫无意义
[But if we look closer,
但如果我们稍加细心
we can see why these alliances formed]
就会发现人们结盟的真正原因
[After all,a shared purpose can give even mortal enemies common ground]
毕竟,共同的目的甚至 能让两个死敌走到一起
Bree,
Bree
we have a question for you
我们有个问题要问
Oh,what is it?
哦,是什么问题
Well,we were just wondering,actually,we were curious about...uh...
我们想知道... 其实,我们是好奇...
What the hell is going on with you and Betty Applewhite?
你和Betty Applewhite到底怎么回事?
Yeah,that
恩,就是这个问题
Excuse me
你说什么
Well,from the day that dead body showed up,
从那个死尸出现的那天开始
nobody was yelling 'oh,the Applewhites are involved other than you
除了你,就没别人说 “哦,Applewhites一家来了”
and the next thing we know,you are having Betty over for poker?
一眨眼的功夫,你又请Betty来打牌？
What???
到底怎么回事
She makes it sound like we are angry,we are not angry
她说得好象我们很生气一样 其实没有
I'm a little angry
我有点生气了
Can we talk about this later? I have ice-cream in here
能以后再说吗,我袋子里装了冰淇淋
Bree,could this flip-flop have something to do with
Bree,这么大的转弯会不会
the fact that Daniel is dating Matthew?
与Daniel和Matthew约会有关？
Yeah,that would get her
恩,这么说她就注意了
Who told you that?
谁告诉你的?
- Mrs. McClosky
- McClosky太太
she saw them making out in the park
她看到他们在公园里亲热
- Eddie!
What?
怎么了?
Can't you sugar-coat a little?
你就不能婉转一点？
I did,he had his hand down her shirt
我有啊 他都把手伸到她衣服里了我还没说呢
Bree,we know that you have a good reason for wanting Betty to hang out with us
Bree,我们知道你让Betty加入 肯定有合适的理由
We just wondered if you could clue us in a little
我们只想稍微了解一下
When it comes to Betty Applewhite,I know what I'm doing
和Betty Applewhite有关的事 我都心里有数
and you two are just gonna have to trust me
你们俩只要相信我
and if you can't do that,
如果你们做不到
then perhaps I've over-estimated the depth of our friendship
那也许我高估了我们的感情
Now,if you excuse me
恕不奉陪了
What a bitch!
婊子一个!
- Eddie,can you ...
- Eddie,你能不能 ...
I was sugar-coating it
我已经很委婉了
Oh,hey...none of that in ear
哦,嘿...别亲耳朵啊
Come on,maybe if we are remind them I'm shacking up with a senior VP,
好了,也许让他们知道我和副总裁是一家的
they'll stop killing all my pitches
他们就不会否决我的创意了
You've only been here for a week,why don't you give yourself a break?
你刚来一个星期,干吗不休息休息?
Honey,you know the ad game,
亲爱的  你也知道广告界的规矩
we got to serve amount of time before mockery kicks me into the curb
不努力就被淘汰
Look,I'm just asking you ...
我只是想让你...
jump in every once in a while,throw me some of the ??? on the work path
时不时地参与一下 在工作上帮我一把
I can't protect you,you're gonna have to find a way to click with Ed yourself
我不能袒护你 你得自己想办法和Ed沟通
And then the pig,he rubs on his stomach,and he goes...'
然后这支猪蹭了蹭肚皮 说到...
Farm Fresh Bacon? I'll make a piggy out of you too'
“来点新鲜农场熏肉吗？ 你也可以一样强壮”
So...
这么说...
the pig actually eats the bacon?
这猪还真要把肉吃下去？
Uhuh,yeah
对
I don't see the client doing a happy dance over the whole cannibalism theme
我看拿自相残杀的主题 可很难让客户买帐
Well,Tom,why don't you pitch them the other idea you came up with last night?
Tom,干吗不说说你昨天晚上 想到的那个点子?
You know,the one where people love bacon so much that they wanna keep it a secret?
就是熏肉大受欢迎 大家都把它当成秘密的那个
What,like a secret underground society of bacon eaters?
怎么,就好比是个熏肉消费者的 秘密地下社会?
Well,like my collage fraternity where,
就和我大学时候的兄弟会差不多
you know,everybody wanted in,but we only take the coolest guys
大家都想往里挤 可我们只要那些最酷的
You were Greek?
你曾经加入Greek?
-Alpha Tau Megon ??
- 是ΑΤΩ
I was Phi Kappa??
我原来是Φκ
You?
就你?
And I don't remember you happened to be that cool to play JTO
我怎么不记得你会酷到玩GTO
Look,if I had a nickle for every fi-cap
如果我还有一枚所有Φκ 在高速公路标志上
that I tag 'naked' to a free way sign
被我贴过“裸体”的纪念币
Scavo,if you were my pledge,I'd make you my bitch
Scavo,如果你立誓加入 那我就让你做我的下手
Oh,you think so?
哦,你这么以为?
You know what,I'm liking this whole fraternity ankle
知道吗  我喜欢这兄弟会的点子
Yeah,you know,let's talk about it over lunch
恩,咱们午饭的时候谈
You're buying
你买单
Go
去啊
Hello,what's going on?
怎么回事?
Gabrielle,I want you to meet someone
Gabrielle,我来给你介绍
This is Xiao Mei
这是小梅
She's the young lady who's forced to work for Maxine Bennett
就是她被Maxine Bennett强制劳役的
Oh,the slave
哦,那个奴隶阿
Wow,
哇
looks well fed
喂得不错啊
The church is making arrangements for her to return to China
教堂正在安排她回中国
But until then,she needs a place to stay
不过在这之前,她需要个落脚的地方
So I offered her our guest room
所以我就把客厅给她住了
Really?
真的啊?
Baby,can I talk to you for a second?
宝贝儿  能跟你说句话吗?
Oh,you nuts
你这个笨蛋
It's only for a couple of days
就那么一两天
Oh,this time,you are quickly becoming Father Crowley's go-to guy for charity cases
那只是这一次吧 你快成了Crowley神父的慈善大使了
And that's a bad thing?
这难道不对?
When he turns our house into a catholic underground ??,YES!
他把咱们家都变成天主教广场了 当然不对！
You know who you are,Gabby?
你知道你属于哪种人么,Gabby?
You are the kind of person who'd turn away Mary and Joseph from the inn
你这种人连圣人都不会让进门半步
Well,they should've called ahead
他们本该先打个电话来的
Don't brush your hair at the table
别在饭桌旁边梳头
Are you talking to me?
你是在和我说话吗?
Does this mean you've finally forgiven me?
那是不是代表你已经原谅我了?
Why should I? You've betrayed this family and you're not even sorry
为什么原谅你？ 你背叛了家人却毫无歉意
Don't be such a drama queen
别这么小题大做的
If the Applewhites go to the police
如果Applewhites家的人去找警察
and tell them that your brother ran over Mrs.Solis,
告诉他们是你哥哥撞了Solis太太
he could go to prison.
他就会坐牢了
How can you not understand that?
你怎么就不懂呢
They won't talk about Andrew as long as you don't go to the police about Caleb
只要你不说Caleb的事 他们就不会提Andrew
What does this Caleb do exactly?
这个Caleb到底是干什么的?
And why on earth are they hiding him?
他们把他藏起来究竟是为了什么?
Why don't you go to Mrs. Applewhite
干吗不去找Applewhite太太
and tell her you really need to know what's going on?
告诉她你想知道事情真相呢?
I bet if you were really nice,she'd tell you the truth
如果你态度够好 我肯定她会告诉你实情的
Is that what you really think,Danielle?
你真的是这么想的吗,Danielle?
I should go to Mrs.Applewhite
我应该去找Applewhite太太
be nice and then she'll hand over all her secrets?
和生和气地让她告诉我所有的秘密？
Yeah
对
When I was young,my stepmother told me that I was very lucky
在我小的时候 我的后妈说我很幸运
I possessed beauty,wit,cunning and insight
我拥有美貌,才智,心计,与见识
These four weapons all women needed to survive in the world
这是全世界的女人都需要的 四种武器
So?
所以呢?
So take good care of your looks,Danielle
所以专注于你的美貌,Danielle
You don't have any other weapons at your disposal
除了这，你一无所有
Hi,
嗨
I need an operation on my spleen,
我要做脾手术
and I just found out that I ran out of medical insurance.
可我刚刚发现我没有医疗保险
Is there anyone I can sue?
有什么我可以起诉的人吗?
After the ????? Launy let the policy lapse
自从我的经纪人垮台后
Now he's in jail,and I'm gonna die
现在他坐牢了 我要死了
Susie,you are not gonna die
Susie, 你不会死的
I'll get into it with the insurance company
我会去找保险公司
No,there isn't time for you to deal with the red tape
不,现在没有时间去繁文缛节了
My spleen is going crinin into my heart
我的脾已经刺激到我的心脏
I need that operation now
我得马上就动手术
I'd loan you the money myself
我本来可以自己借钱给你
But Eddie and I just plopped down our savings since ski condo
可Eddie和我已经把积蓄都花在房子上了
I don't need a loan
我不需要借钱
I need coverage
我需要保险
I mean what if there are complications
如果要是有并发症可怎么办
I don't have a safety net
我连一点保障也没有
...please...
...求你了...
What in the hell are you doing?
你到底在干吗?
I'm saying a little prayer
我在祈祷
Uh,for puke sake
啊,看在呕吐的份上
What? I'm desperate here,do you have any other ideas?
怎么,我已经走投无路了 你还有其他办法吗?
As a matter of fact,I do
其实  我有办法
What you need is a husband
你需要的,是个丈夫
What?
什么?
The only way to get a good health plan
获得健康唯一办法
is to marry into one
就是嫁人
Eddie,come on
Eddie,拜托
No,no,I think she's onto something
别,我觉得她说得有道理
Yeah,if we find the guy with the right plan
如果我们找到了合适人选
you could have a sham waiting on a  Monday night,and be
你就可以周一结婚
fully covered Tuesday morning
周二就有医保了
I can't believe you are actually considering this
不敢相信你还真的会考虑这个办法
The surgeon is slicing me open a week from tomorrow,
还有一周我就要开刀了
what other choice do I have?
还能有什么办法?
All we have to do is to find a guy who's willing to marry you
只要找到一个愿意娶你的人就行
You know,come to think of it,
仔细想想
a little prayer might not be such a bad idea after all
也许祈祷并不是个坏主意
Pad,we are all here,so send the call in as soon as you get it
Pad,我们都在 接到电话就马上转进来吧
200 bucks says you can't do that three times in a row
我出200块赌你不能连续接三次
You catch three of those,
连续三次
200 bucks
就有200块
What do you say there,Scavo?
怎么样,Scavo?
You are on.
开始吧
- Here we go.
- 开始
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
啊啊啊啊！
Thrown by me.
我来扔
I'm sorry,I thought we were here to talk aboutthe farm fresh rollout?
抱歉, 我以为我们是来讨论农场首场展示
They gotta be catchable,big guy.
它们会被我接住的,伙计
You just let me worryabout the shooting.
你让我担心该怎样投了
Come on.
来吧
- that's one.
- 一个
Guys...
伙计们...
oh!
噢！
Nice moves.
漂亮
One more,big guy.
又一个,伙计
Guys,please... that's--all right.
伙计们,拜托... 好吧
- Ow!
- 啊噢！
Oh!
噢！
ow.
噢
that wasn't even catchable!
那怎么接的住！
Yeah,well,maybe not.
恩,可能不是
But it's totally worth the 200 bucks.Ahh!
但是这足足值200美元
Whoo!
呼！
Well,you got me.
你该给我的
You're a regularlittle monkey man!
你真是只猴子
Oh,I love this guy.
噢,我爱这家伙
Oh. Hi.
噢,你好
Do you have to sit aroundall day?
你得坐一整天么？
I mean,shouldn't you be out experiencingwestern civilization
我是说,你不是应该出去体验一下 西方文明
while you have the chance?
当你有这个机会的时候？
what are you doing?
你在做什么？
I fix.
我在补...
No,this is couture!
不,这是名牌！
This rip has to be fixedby an experienced tailor.
这裂缝得让经验丰富的裁缝来补
You can't just...
你不能...
holy crap!This stitching is perfect!
噢天呐！缝的真漂亮！
Hungry?
饿了么？
Did you make all of this?
都是你做的？
Oh!
噢！
For me? Okay.
给我的？好的
Oh,my god!
噢,天呐！
You like?
你喜欢？
I like a lot.
非常喜欢
you like that?
你喜欢这个？
yeah,that's nice.
是的,非常不错
Do you know what they do to people in china who speak out against the government?Hmm?
你知道在中国他们怎么对付那些 要反抗政府的人么？嗯？
They put themin forced labor camps.
他们得进劳改所
Isn't that awful?
很可怕,不是么？
Mm-hmm.
嗯哼
You know what I mean?It's such a repressive regime.
你知道我在说什么么？ 这是一个多么高压的政治制度
We forgethow good we have it.
我们都忘了这方面上我们多么幸运
Yes,we do.
是的
Don't you think xiao-mei would like it better herein america?
你不觉得小梅会更喜欢在美国么？
I mean,where she could learn about freedom and democracyand stuff?
我是说,她能在这体会 什么是自由和民主
Does this haveanything to do with you making xiao-meido housework?
这和你让小梅做家务有什么关系么？
What?
什么？
I came downstairs this morningand found her waxing the floor.
我早上下楼的时候看见她在给 地板上蜡
She told me you asked herto put on two coats.
她告诉我说你让她穿2件衣服
Well,first of all,that was her idea.
好吧,首先,这是她的主意
Second of all,I can't have this conversation until you've tasted her crab puffs.
其次,我们得等你尝过她做的 螃蟹泡芙以后再继续讨论这个
Oh...
噢...
She just got donebeing a slave.
她只是不幸的做了奴隶
I mean,she wantsto go back to china...
我是说,她想回中国...
and we can't force herto stay here and be our maid.
我们也不能勉强她在这里做 我们的女佣
Well,who's forcing her? We'll pay herwhatever she wants.
谁强迫她了？我们会给她所有她 想要的
And the best part is,with her rsum?
最棒的就是,以她的资历
any wage will look good.
工资会不错
No way,baby. Mnh-mnh.
不行,宝贝
What?
怎么了？
What? What,so you don't getwhat you want, you just walk offand pout?
怎么？你不能得到你想要的 就撅撅嘴走开么？
Oh,this isn't about me.
噢,这不是我的问题
This is about our great nation.
而是关乎我们伟大的国家
And I have no intentionof sexually satisfying a man who isn't willing to stand up for
并且我也不想取悦一个不想支持
and help spread the ideals and values of the united statesof america.
和帮助传播美国观念和价值的男人
And sometimes she is a little hard to stomach,but she means well.
虽然有时候她让人难以忍受 但是总体来说不错
Well,that's--
好吧,就是说--
hi!Oh,here she is.
你好！噢,她来了
I came as soon as I got your message.
我一收到你的短信就来了
Is this... this is gary grantham
这是... 这是加里﹒格兰瑟姆
your future ex-husband.
你未来的准丈夫
- Wow,nice to meet you.
- 哇哦,很高兴见到你
Hi.
你好
Okay,listen,um,I've got to meet a client. I've got to go,
好吧,听着,嗯,我还有个 客户要见,现在得走了
so just talk amongst yourselves, and
那么随便聊聊
you two makea very handsome couple.
你们真是一对俊男美女
Oh.Yeah.
噢,好吧
Uh, hi.
- 嗨
hi.
嗨
So do you wannaget married on wednesday?
你愿意在星期三结婚么？
'Cause thursday and fridayI'm out of town.
因为星期四和星期五我不在这儿
Oh! Oh,yeah. Sure,that's--wednesday's great.
噢！噢,可以.当然,我是说-- 星期三很不错
I'm--I'm just curious...
我--我只是好奇...
how did edie convince youto do this so quickly?
伊迪是怎么在这么短的时间内 就说服你的？
Well,she explainedyour situation to me.
他跟我说明了你的情况
I'm sort of in needof a fake bride myself, so I figured,
我正急着找一个挂名新娘 所以我同意了
what the heck?
管它的
Why would you needa fake bride?
为什么你需要一个挂名新娘
Uh,I'm gay,and I've nevercome out to my mother.
啊,我是个同性恋,并且我永远 无法对我妈妈坦诚这件事
- Really?
- 真的？
Yeah.
是的
At first,I justdidn't want to upset her.
开始,我只是不想让她难过
Then she got older,she gotemphysema and diverticulitis,
后来她年纪大了 得了肺气肿和憩室炎
and I started thinking,if I just kept my mouth shut,
我开始思考,只要我闭口不提
then one day naturewould take its course
她终将离开
and we could avoid what is sureto be a very ugly scene.
那我们就可以避免一个必定 非常糟糕的场面
So what changed?
那么是什么改变了？
She told me at her81st birthday party last month,
上个月在她81岁生日的时候 她告诉我
the only reason she's hanging onis to see me get married.
她坚持到现在的唯一原因是 希望能看到我结婚
Oh. Oh,so by marrying me...
噢。噢,所以只要和我结婚...
yeah,I'd get my inheritancethat much sooner.
是的,我也将更快得到遗产
No,but mostly,I wanna make sure she's happy.
不,最主要的是,我想让她开心
well,you seemvery nice,susan.
你看起来非常不错,Susan
Uh,it will be a pleasurebeing married to you.
啊,和你结婚会是一件非常令人 愉快的事
Uh,likewise.
啊,彼此彼此
here,you can finishthe rest of the fries.
就这样,你可以把剩下的吃完
Here's your mail
这是你的信
and your pills.
还有药
Ugh.
啊
More pills?
更多的药？
Miss tillman?
Tilman小姐
Hmm?
嗯？
Where did this come from?
这是从哪儿寄来的？
I don't know.It was in with your other mail.
我不知道 它只是和别的信混在一起
Get me the phone.
把电话给我
Sullivan,it's me.
沙拉文,是我
I just got some news,and I need to get you involved.
我刚得到一些消息 并且有必要把你扯进来
Looks like delfino'sbeen holding out on me.
看样子Delfino对我隐瞒了一些事
The next morning,bree came up with a plan
第二天早晨,Bree想好了一个
to get to the truth she so desperately needed.
查知她迫切想知道德真相的计划
As she watched the applewhites leave their house,
当她看着Applewhites离开了她的家
she thought of how much she had trusted the previous owners
她想起她曾多么相信这个前任业主
and how much they...
还有他们一度那么的...
had trusted her.
相信她
caleb? Is that you?
Caleb?是你么？
hi.
你好
I'm bree.I live down the street.
我是Bree,我住在这条街上
I'm a friendof your mother'S.
我是你妈妈的朋友
She's not home.
她不在家
I know. Um...
我知道 嗯...
I came to see you.
我是来见你的
- Me?
- 我？
Yes.
是的
Your mother told meall about you and I thought it--
你妈妈告诉了我你的一切 我觉得--
it might be nice if,um,
如果我们能见一面,嗯
we had a little visit.
会更好
I brought yousome homemade cobbler.
我给你带了一些自己做的 脆皮点心
oh,la,la,la,la,la
噢,拉,拉,拉,拉,拉
right here.Follow the doughnut,people.
就在这儿,跟着这个油炸圈饼
Here we go. We got some people.Come on,come on.
我们现在就去。我们有些人了 来吧,来吧
Hey,hey What's going on?
嘿嘿,发生什么事了？
Well,um,ed bet tom thathe wouldn't eat a doughnut out of the toilet.
嗯,Ed跟Tom打赌他绝对吃不下 一个从厕所取出的甜甜圈
Isn't it disgusting?
这不是很恶心么？
unh-unh!
啊－啊！
It's gottabe fully dunked.
它必须被完全浸泡
Now,I don't want the glazeto repel the water.
听着,我可不想表面上沾着水
Whoa,slight delay,people.I'm requesting a scrub down.
稍等一下,伙计们 我要求擦一下
Does anybody know wherethey keep the toilet brush?
谁知到他们把刷子放在哪里了么？
Just for one second,okay?Just for one second.
1秒钟,好么？就等1秒钟
Hey,I never thoughtI'd have to ask you this,
嘿,我从没想过我会问你这个问题
but are you about to eat a doughnut out of the toilet?
但是你真的打算吃一个从厕所 捞出来的甜甜圈？
Yeah!
正是！
For the galveston jewelersaccount.
为了Galveston的宝石帐目
I don't care!
我不在乎这个！
You're not gonna do this!
你不能这么做！
Look,lynette, you're the one who told meto find a way to click with ed.
听着,lynette 是你让我找个方法和ed交涉
Well,now we've got our thing,
现在我们得到了我们要的
and it's paying off for me!
它将给我钱
That's because ed gets offon humiliating you.
那是因为Ed在羞辱你
Please,don't do this!
求求你,别这么做！
We're waiting,scavo!
我们在等你,Scavo！
This is my moment.
这是我的决定
so,caleb,besides your mother and brother,
那么,Caleb,除了你妈妈和哥哥
does anybody elseknow that you're here?
还有别人知道你在这儿么？
No.
没有
You're pretty.
你很漂亮
thank you.That's very sweet.
谢谢,很高兴听你这么说
So where have you been livingthis whole time? Upstairs?
那么这些时间你都住哪儿？楼上？
No.
不是
I just moved upstairs.
我刚搬到楼上
My room's downstairs.
我的房间在楼下
Downstairs?
楼下？
In the basement.
在地下室
You wanna see it?
你想看一下吗？
Caleb,have you been down hereall these months?
Caleb,你这几个月一直待在这儿？
Yeah.
是的
Did your mothermake you wear those?
你妈妈给你戴着这些？
Most of the time.
大部分时间是这样
Oh,my god!
天啊
Sweetheart,I don't understand.
亲爱的,我不明白
Why in the world wouldyour mother treat you that way?
究竟为什么你妈妈这样待你？
I hurt a girl.
我伤害了一个女孩
A girl?
一个女孩？
Yeah.
是的
And then she died.
然后她死了
Oh.
哦
Her name was melanie.
她叫梅兰尼
She was pretty.
她很美
Just like you.
就像你
Hi.
嗨!
I thought you should know,I'm getting married.
我觉得你应该知道,我要结婚了
To the doctor?
和医生
No! No. Ha!
不！不是,哈！
No,to--to a gay guy.
不是,和...和个同性恋
How did you knowabout the doctor?
你怎么知道那个医生的？
People talk. So you--
别人说的,那么...
you're marrying a gay guy?
你和一个同性恋结婚？
I need health insurance,
我需要医疗保险
um,'cause I've gotthis wandering spleen and...
嗯,因为我的脾脏会游动
that sounds funny, "spleen wandering," but...
好玩儿吧,“脾会游动” 但是...
actually,it's not funny 'causeit can bang into things...
事实上,这并不好玩 因为它会撞到其它器官...
so I need health insurance,so I'm getting married tomorrow.
所以我需要医疗保险 所以我明天要结婚
And you probably thinkI'm crazy,right?
肯定认为我疯了,对吧？
Well... can it wait?
那...可以等吗？
Um,the surgery?
我说那手术？
No.
不
It can't wait.
不能等
I guess it's really not that crazy.
我觉得没那么疯狂
how you doin',ma'am?
你好,女士
Susan,can you justgive me a minute?
苏珊,可以等我一下吗？
Oh,yeah.No,I'm sorry.
呃,好的,对不起
I--that was really... it.
我...实在是...
What do you want?
你想要什么？
It's not what i want,delfino.
不是我要什么,Delfino
It's whatnoah taylor wants.
而是Taylor想要
Where's his grandkid?
他的孙娃在哪儿？
You know,let's skip the part where you don't knowanything about anything.
你看 就不要再说你什么都不知道
Mr. Taylor wants to chat.
Taylor先生想聊一聊
What if I say no?
如果我说不呢？
Then I've gottafind the kid myself,
那我得自己去找那孩子
and my guess is,he or she issomewhere around here close.
那我猜他或者她就在这附近吧
Your old girlfriend--
你的前女友...
she's got a daughter,right?
她有一个女儿,对吧？
Maybe I should startby paying her a visit...
也许我应该去拜访一下她
her daughter's not the one.
不是她女儿
Yeah,well,given your track record,
啊,这个,考虑到你的前科
I might wanna check that outfor myself.
我可能得自己去查
Tell him I'll be therein the morning.
告诉他我早上会去见他
Oh!
哦
So pretty.
真漂亮
You like nice things?
你喜欢好看的东西？
that's why I think you're stupid,
那就是我觉得你很傻的原因
for not wanting to stay here.
因为你居然不想留下来
You could be around my nice things all the time,
我的漂亮东西会一直陪伴 在你左右
taking care of them...
照看它们...
how fun would that be?
那多有趣啊！
Well,I'm sure it's a lotmore fun than you'd have in that
肯定比你待在你那个
tiny,godforsaken village of yours.
偏远的小村子好多了
You know,we're probably more alike than people would guess.
你看,别人也许想象不到 我们有一些相似之处
I'm from a small town,too.
我也来自一个小镇
My folks had nothing.
我父母一无所有
That's why I love america.
那就是我喜欢美国的原因
Anything is possible.
一切皆有可能
Oh...
哦
hmm,you like that?
恩,你喜欢那个？
No.
不
An old,fat stock broker gave this to me.
一个又老又胖的股票交易员给我的
It's not worth anything.You can have it.
不值什么钱,你拿去吧
Oh...
哦...
oh!
哦！
It's okay.Glad you like it.
没什么,你喜欢就好
You can brush my hair.
你可以帮我梳头了
Oh!
哦！
- Hi.
- 嗨
Hi.
嗨
Uh,this is the bestI could do on such short notice.
在这么短的时间内 我已经尽力做到最好了
- Okay. - Okay.
- 很好,很好
Oh,uh,susan,this is,uh,my best man,steven.
哦,呃,苏珊,这是 呃,我的伴郎史蒂夫
He's also my life partner.
也是我的另一半
Oh,hi.It's nice to meet you.
哦,你好,很高兴见到你
Baby,be--be nice.Come on.
亲爱的,友好点儿好吗？
I'm sorry you have cancer.
真遗憾,你得了癌症
Cancer?
癌症？
Isn't that the point of this whole charade?
这不正是这场游戏的意义所在吗？
Gary said you needed insurance.
加里说你需要医保
Oh,yes. No,no,I do need insurance.
哦,是的,不不,我确实需要医保
I just don't have cancer.I have A...
只是我得的不是癌症,而是...
wandering spleen.
游动脾
I said it was like cancer.
我说的是和癌症差不多的病
Is there a problem?
有什么问题吗？
No.No,everything's fine.
不不,没什么
Uh,let's just go to the chapel.
呃,我们进教堂吧
Shall we?
可以吗？
I made a wedding cake.
我做了个结婚蛋糕
I hope you enjoy it.
希望你喜欢
Oh! Uh...
哦！哦...
so... are we ready to get started?
那么,我们可以开始了？
Oh,do you have a thing to play music?
哦,你们有什么可以放音乐的东西吗？
I had steven burn a little wedding mix for us,.
我叫史蒂夫给我们作了个 小小的混音婚礼进行曲...
for ambience
来调动气氛
Sure,just,um,give me a sec
好的,恩,请等一下
do you have a problem?
你有什么问题吗
You said she was sick.
你说她病了
She is.
她的确病了
She has a wandering spleen.
她得了游动脾
It sounds nothing like cancer. It doesn't even sound real.
听上去它可不像癌症 甚至不像一种真的病
Well,it is. I-I could die.
啊,它是一种病 我,我可能会死的
You look fine to me,honey.
亲爱的,我觉得你看上去一点事也没有
Don't do this.
别这样
I have asked you six times to fly with me to holland to get married,
我曾经六次叫你和我 一起飞到荷兰去结婚
and you always have some la me excuse.
但是你总有莫名其妙的借口
But the second some chick with a silly disease comes along,
当这个得了一种可笑的病 的二手货出现时
well,you drop everything and head for a chapel.
你就什么也不顾地跑到教堂来了
Oh,no,it's a serious illness.
哦,不,这是一种非常严重的病
See,it just sounds silly'cause of the word "spleen."
病名只是听起来很可笑 因为有个“脾”字
What do you want from me?
你要我怎么做
I want you to worry about my feelings half as much as you worry about your mother's!
我只是想你像关心 你妈妈一半那样关心我
What is it gonna take to make you happy?
你要怎样才高兴呢？
Not go through with the wedding?
不举行这个婚礼了？
Is that what you're asking?
这就是你想要的吗？
Oh,oh! No,no,stop right there.
哦哦！不不,打住
Okay,I would love to see you two crazy kids get hitched in holland more than anyone,
听着,我巴不得你们这对爱人在荷兰成家
with the tulips and the clogs,in front of a windmill,the whole shebang.
有郁金香！有木底鞋！ 有风车！还有小酒店！
But unless I get this surgery,
但如果我不做手术
my spleen is going to slam straight into my heart and explode.
我的脾就会撞进我的心脏然后爆炸
So,you know,seeing as I am just a nice person
所以,你看,看在我是个好人的份儿上
and I always support gay rights,let's just do this.
而且我一向支持同性恋的权利 举行婚礼吧
And then I'll have a husband and insurance.
这样我就能有个丈夫,得到医保
Nobody gets hurt.
没有人会受到伤害
Steven,why...steven!
史蒂夫,为什么？史蒂夫！
- it's just...
- 真是...
yeah.
是啊
I'm so sorry.
很抱歉
My hands are tied.
我无能为力
I'm really sorry.
实在抱歉
Steven,wait. Steven... where are you going?
史蒂夫,等等,史蒂夫...你去哪儿？
Ah,finally got the sound system working.
啊,音响终于好了
Where's the groom?
新郎在哪儿？
Hey,susie Q.
嗨, Suzzi小可爱
What's wrong? For a newlywed,you don't have much spring in your step.
怎么了？ 一个新嫁娘不该这么垂头丧气啊
I didn't get married.
我没结成婚
Really?
真的？
We got to the altar, but the whole fake wedding thing sort of imploded.
我们到了祭坛 但是整个假婚礼搞砸了
Wow. I'm sorry.
哇啊,我很遗憾
I still don't have insurance.
我还是没有医保
I need to get that operation. I'M...
我需要做那个手术,我...
I'm really screwed.
这下完了
well...
呃...
why don't I just marry you?
干嘛不嫁给我呢？
What?
什么？
I've got a fantastic health plan.
我有很好的医疗保险
You'd be covered instantly.
婚后你能立刻能拿到
But... we were actually married.
但是...我们结过婚啊
Look,susie,I've always felt awful about walking out on you the way I did.
看吧,Susan 我一直对离开你这件事感到不安
And I figure,if we do this,
所以我想,如果我们结婚
I'd basically be saving your life.
至少我可以救你一命
I figure I owe you one.
我想这是我欠你的
Karl...
so what do you say?
怎样？
Will you marry me,susan mayer?
你愿意嫁给我吗,Susan Mayer？
again?
再一次的？
What the hell?
干嘛不呢？
cool!
好！
what are we gonna do about edie?
Eddie怎么办呢？
- We can't tell her.
- 我们不能告诉她
She'd kill us both.
她会杀了我俩
Yeah,it'll be our little secret.
是啊,这是我们的小秘密
We've really enjoyed having you as a guest. Right,gaby?
真的很高兴你在此做客,是吧,Gabi？
Absolutely.
当然
Xiao-mei,you are a very special girl, so...
小梅,你是一个非常特殊的女孩 那...
so you take care,okay?
那你要保重,好吗？
Oh!
噢！
hanks for all your help,carlos.
多谢你拔刀相助,Carlos
my pleasure,father.
我的荣幸,神父
- Bye-bye.
- 拜拜
Ladies?
女士们？
please don't tell me you're crying
别告诉我你在哭
just because you can'thave the maid you want.
是因为你太想要这个女佣
Carlos,she wouldn't have been just a maid.
Carlos,她不只是个普通女佣
She would have been the best damn maid ever.
她可是万里挑一
God,you're pathetic.
天,你真可怜
Shut up.
闭嘴
hey,
嘿
something's going on.
来看看
is there a problem?
发生了什么？
Well,xiao-mei doesn't wantto go back to china.
小梅不想回中国去
She wants to stay here and work for you.
他想留在这里给你们干活
What? Why?
什么？ 为什么？
she says mrs. Solis treated her with more kindness than she's ever known.
她说Solis太太对她非常好
She now thinks of you two as family.
她已经把你们当成家人
Oh,really?
噢,真的？
Oh,of course you can stay!
当然,你可以留下！
gaby...
Gaby...
carlos,she thinks of us as family.
Carlos,她把我们当成家人
I'm ready to heart hose farm fresh concepts.
我准备好听你们的新提议
Conference room in five...
会议室五点
toilet boy!
厕所男孩！
you are so not allowed to complain to me.
不准你向我吐苦水
I know. You were right,okay?
我知道,你是对的,好吧？
So now I'm known throughout the advertising world as "toilet boy."
现在我是广告圈众所周知的 厕所男孩
Tell him you're done with the games.
告诉他你已经受够这些游戏
You don't wanna play anymore.
你不想再玩下去
No,no,no,I can'T.I can'T.
不不不 ,我办不到
If I back down now,he'll see it as a sign of weakness. Look,
如果我现在放弃 他就会看出我一丝懦弱.听着
this is the way that guys do business.But--
这就是男人做生意的道,但-
so you called it.
如果你要硬来
He made me his bitch.
他会让我颜面扫地
Come on.
来吧
Here you go.Oh.
给你
You know,ed,I've been thinking.
你知道,我一直在想
We've had a lot of fun and games around here lately,
最近这里气氛异常轻松活泼
but maybe it's time to set a slightly more professional tone in the office.
也许现在应该让办公室里 添几分严肃
Oh,I get it.
噢,我明白了
Somebody went running to mommy,didn't he? Huh?
有人叫妈咪了,是吗？
What?
什么？
Tom loses a few bets,
Tom输掉几个赌
so he tries to get his wife to make me back off?
所以他让老婆来收摊儿？
Oh,this is so alpha tau.
这可不是兄弟会的规矩
I am gonna make him pay.
我会让他亲自偿还
No. No,you're not gonna make him pay.
不不,你不能这么做
You are gonna stop this now.
你现在就要收手
This is my company.
这是我的公司
If people wanna work here,they play by my rules.
如果人们想在这里干活 就按我的游戏规则行事
- Ed!
- Ed！
What?
什么？
I'm calling you out.
我要和你一赌
Huh?
- 恩？
Yes,you're right.
你说得对
This is your company,so I'll play by your rules.
这是你的公司 那我要按你的游戏规则行事
What do I have to do to get youto stop this frat boy crap?
我要怎么办才能让你罢手
Shave my eyebrows?Come to work naked?
刮掉眼睫毛？ 不穿衣服上班？
Name your stakes.
悉听尊便
I don't have time for this.
没时间开玩笑
Aw,what's wrong,ed?
怎么了,Ed?
You afraid a phi kapp'sgonna get beaten by a girl?
你害怕一个玩兄弟会的 会被一个小妞打败？
Come on,big man...
来啊,大男人
it's just a little bet.
只是一个小赌
As you know,I thinkthat making the workplace fun is good for morale.
我认为在办公场所增添一些乐趣 有利于员工士气
But lynette here thinksthat our shenanigans have gottena little out of hand.
但Lynette认为我们的恶作剧 显然玩过头了
oh,hold on. Hold on.
别忙别忙
I respect lynette's work ethic.
我尊重Lynette的工作原则
So we've decidedto settle the matter with a little testof intestinal fortitude.
所以我们决定摆平这件事 通过勇气考验
If she can eat
如果她能吃下
1 pound of our client's fine,farm-fresh pork product,
1磅来自我们客户优质新鲜的 猪肉产品
raw...
生吃...
there'll be a moratoriumon wagering in the office.
那么办公室里的恶作剧 将告一段落
oh,oh!
噢！
I knowyou are doing this for me.
我知道你这是为了我
You don't need to do this.
没有这个必要
I don't need you fighting my fights.
我不需要你为我扛
I am not fighting your fights.
我不是为你
This is my fight
是为我自己
this is how guysdo business,right?
这就是你们做生意的行道 对吗？
While we're young.
趁我们还年轻
no shame in defeat,lynette.
输了也不会羞耻,Lynette
No shame at all.
完全不会
oh,she's gonna do it.
噢,她要开动了
ohh!
噢！
oh,yes!
噢,好样的！
oh!
噢！
oh,this is too much.
噢,那太多了
oh!
噢
what?
怎么了？
She took the bet.
是她要打这个赌
What? This is fun,people.
怎么了？这很有趣,伙计们
she's got one more.
她只剩最后一片了
so...
所以...
can this be a placeof business again,ed?
这里能回到干正经事的地方么,ed？
- No more games?
- 不再游戏了？
Sure.
当然
You sucked all the funout of it anyway.
总之你抹杀了所有的乐子
that was really something.
你真伟大
Thanks.
谢谢
Could you scrounge me upa bucket?
你能帮我找个桶来么？
Caleb saida nice,red-haired lady came to visit him.
Caleb说有个漂亮,红头发的女士 探望过他
Come on in,betty.
进来吧,Betty
Get you a drink?
喝点什么？
This is nota social call,bree!
这可不是光明正大,Bree！
Did you or did you not breakinto my home and talk to my son?
你偷偷潜入我家跟我的儿子谈话？
Caleb and I had,uh,a very lovely chat. Yes.
Caleb跟我进行了,啊, 非常愉快的交谈,是的
if you evercome near him again,
如果你再接近他
there will be hellto pay. Do you understand?
代价可能是致命的 明白了么？
Aren't you gonna ask mewhat we talked about?
你不问问我们谈了什么么？
The name,um...
那个人,嗯...
melanie foster came up.
提到了Melanie Foster
I'm gonna pour youa drink now,betty,
我倒点喝的给你吧,betty
because we're about to havea very honest discussion,
因为我们将要进行一番 非常诚恳的讨论
and I think you're gonnaneed a little help getting through it.
并且我认为你需要一些帮助去 想想这件事
his name's zach young.
他的名字叫Zach Young
He lives with his father.
和他爸爸一起住
Mother committed suicideabout a year ago.
母亲在一年前自杀
How did he end upwith these people?
他是怎样与这些人了断的？
How do you think?
你怎么想？
Dierdre was strung out,noah.She gave him up.
Dierdre 当时染上了毒品 她放弃了他
I wanna see this boy.
我想见见这个男孩
Well,he's gota new family now. I can't just snap my fingersand get him in here.
现在,他有了个新家 我不能强迫他到这儿来
Maybe not,but I can snap my fingers,
你或许不能,但我做得到
and detective sullivan can make it happen.
Sullivan侦探会让它发生的
- You don't wanna do that.
- 你不会这么做的
No?
不会？
Is that reallythe way you wanna meet him--
这真的想这么见他？
have that thug drag him in hereso grandpa can give him a hug?
让那个暴徒把他拖到这儿 而因此他的祖父可以拥抱他？
Fine. You bring him.I'll give you two days.
好吧,你把他带来 我给你2天的时间
As you know,I'm on a bitof a clock here.
你知道的,我在这儿的时间不多
When caleb was born,
Caleb出生的时候
and the doctors discovered that he was different,
医生发现他有些不同
I didn't even cry.
我甚至没有哭
It was the most painful moment of my life.
那是我这一生中最痛苦的一刻
I didn't shed a single tear.
但我没有流一滴眼泪
I just thought to myself,what's the point?
我只是问自己,什么是最重要的？
He is my son,
他是我儿子
and I haveto raise him
我得抚养他
as best I can.
尽我所能
Now that's my job.
那是我的责任
In a lot of ways,I feel so blessed.
在很多方面,我觉得很幸福
Caleb is challenged,
Caleb遭遇不幸
but he has such a sweet nature.
但他本性非常善良
I'm sure you noticed thatwhen you came to visit.
我敢肯定当你去看他的时候 就注意到了
Yes,I did.
是的
I also noticed that you had himchained in the basement.
我还知道你把他锁在地下室
That's becauseof melanie foster.
那是因为melanie foster.
Melanie was a girlthat matthew dated.
Melanie是和Matthew约会过的女孩
She was a debutante.
她涉世未深
And liketypical teenagers,
就像典型的青少年一样
their relationshipwas full of drama.
他们的关系充满了戏剧性
They were always breaking upand getting back together and breaking up.
他们总是分了又合,合了又分
One night,after oneof their big blow-ups,
一个晚上,他们其中一次的大争吵后
caleb somehow convinced melanie to meet him downat our local lumberyard.
Caleb不知怎么说服了Melanie 在我们当地的木场见面
I can only imagine thatshe thought he was bringing some kind of apology from matthew
我只能猜想她认为他是 帮Matthew道歉来的
but he wasn'T.
但他不是
Caleb told melanie
Caleb告诉Melanie
he was in love with her,
他爱上她了
and thatif he was her boyfriend,
如果他是她的男朋友
he would neverbreak up with her...
他永远不会和她分手
and she laughedin his face.
她笑他
He tried to show herhe was serious by kissing her...
他试着吻她来表示他是认真的...
and she hit him.
她打了他
He doesn't remember a lotof what happened after that,but he--
他不记得后面发生了什么,但是--
he does know thathe got very,very angry,and...
他肯定他非常,非常的生气,并且...
and that there was an axlying on the ground nearby him.
那儿有把斧头在他附近
Yes,
是的
my caleb killed melanie,
我的Caleb杀了Melanie
but I couldn'tlet him go to jail...
但是我不能让他去坐牢...
or worse,be put down,
或者更糟的,被处决
for what was really my crime.
而事实上是我的罪行
Your crime?
你的罪行？
It was my responsibility.
是我的责任
I was supposedto protect him from himself.
我应该保护他
I am his mother.
我是他母亲
That was my job.
那是我的责任
The world is filled with unlikely friendships.
这个世界充满了不可能发生 而发生的友情
How do they begin?
要问他们是怎么开始的？
With one person desperately in need,
一个有着迫切需要
and another willing to lend a helping hand.
而另一个愿意伸出援助之手
When such kindness is offered...
当有了这样的仁慈...
We're finally able to see the worth of those we had previously written off.
我们最终得以见到我们之前 所做的一切的价值
And before we know it...
在我们知道以前...
a bond has formed,
一条连系彼此的纽带就已成形
regardless of whether others can understand it.
不管别人是否能理解...
Yes,unlikely friendships start up every day.
确实如此,意外的情谊 天天都会发生
No one understands this
没有人能理解他
more than the lonely.
比孤独更多
In fact,
事实上
it's what they count on.
这是他们所依赖的
-------------------------- www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents --------------------------
-=伊甸园YTET字幕组=- 谢谢观赏
Sync: YTET-Starry -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=伊甸园YTET字幕组=- 翻译: Bryan,小公窬,Jean,午夜飞行 校对: 午夜飞行 时间轴：Starry